<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<refentry version="5.2" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
  <refmeta>
    <refentrytitle>WebDyne::Constant</refentrytitle>

    <manvolnum>3pm</manvolnum>
  </refmeta>

  <refnamediv>
    <refname>WebDyne::Constant</refname>

    <refpurpose>WebDyne module that sets constants and defaults for WebDyne
    processing</refpurpose>
  </refnamediv>

  <refsynopsisdiv>
    <programlisting>#!env perl
#
use WebDyne::Constant;
print $WEBDYNE_CACHE_DN</programlisting>
  </refsynopsisdiv>

  <refsection>
    <title>Description</title>

    <para>This module provides a list of configuration constants used in the
    WebDyne code. These constants are used to configure the behavior of the
    WebDyne module and can be accessed by importing the module and referencing
    the constants by name. Constants can be configured to different values by
    overriding values in local configuration files, setting environment
    variables, command line options, or Apache directives.</para>

    <para>Common uses for modifying constant value allow for:</para>

    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>Changing default language from en-US</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Modifying or adding new meta-data or default headers to
        output</para>
      </listitem>

      <listitem>
        <para>Adding default style-sheets or other inclusions to all output
        files</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
  </refsection>

  <refsection>
    <title>CONSTANTS</title>

    <para>The following user configurable constants are defined in the module.
    The default value of the configuration constant is provided after the
    constant name:</para>

    <variablelist>
      <varlistentry>
        <term>WEBDYNE_CACHE_DN ()</term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Directory where compiled pages are stored. Unset by default on
          command line, usually set to temporary directory by installer or
          PSGI handler. Pages that are compiled from .psp source into an
          intermediate data structure in Storable format are stored in this
          location. </para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term>WEBDYNE_STARTUP_CACHE_FLUSH (1)</term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Flush cache files at startup. If set will delete all cache
          files and force re-read and recompile of all source .psp files at
          startup. Recommended to leave at (1) </para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term>WEBDYNE_CACHE_CHECK_FREQ</term>

        <listitem>
          <para/>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>
    </variablelist>
  </refsection>
</refentry>
